Perfect Cheesecake. 480 min · 12 servings · American
Ingredients: 9. 1 3/4 cups graham cracker crumbs (about 15 full crackers); 1/3 cup butter, melted; 1/4 cup granulated sugar; 1/2 teaspoon kosher salt
Section: Crust
Step 1. Preheat oven to 350°F.
Step 2. Mix the graham cracker crumbs, butter, granulated sugar, and salt together evenly.
Step 3. Press the mixture into the bottom and up the sides of a 9-inch springform pan.
Step 4. Bake the crust for 8–10 minutes, or until lightly golden. Set aside while you make the cheesecake.
Section: Cheesecake
Step 5. In the bowl of a stand mixer fitted with the paddle attachment, mix the cream cheese and sugar on medium speed until smooth, scraping the sides of th…
Step 6. Turn the mixer to low and add the sour cream and vanilla; mix well, scraping sides of the bowl as necessary.
Step 7. Add the eggs, 1 at a time, mixing on low speed after each addition just until mixed. Don’t overmix.
Step 8. Pour the filling over the crust and spread evenly.
Step 9. Double wrap the bottom of the springform pan with foil, sealing it tightly to prevent water from getting into the pan.
Step 10. Place the springform pan into a larger pan and pour very hot water into the pan until it’s 3/4-inch deep, being careful the water doesn’t come up hi…
You're ready. Use Make It for checkboxes on the page.